(Mrs Cooper:)Did I start that sentence with the words
"if it please Your Highness"?
(Sheldon:)I'm not going to.
I didn't say anything that wasn't true.
(Mrs Cooper:)Now, you listen here.
I have been telling you since you were 4.
(Mrs Cooper:)It's okay to be smarter than everybody,
but you can't go around pointing it out.
- Why not?
- Because people don't like it.
(Mrs Cooper:)Remember all the ass-kickings
from the neighbor kids?
(Mrs Cooper:)Now, let's get cracking.
(Mrs Cooper:)Shower, shirt, shoes and let's shove off.
(Sheldon:)Wouldn't have been any ass-kickings
if that stupid death ray had worked.
(Mrs Cooper:)Problem solved.
(Leonard:)Really? That's impressive.
(Mrs Cooper:)Leonard, the Lord never gives us
more than we can handle.
(Mrs Cooper:)Thankfully, he blessed me
with two other children...
(Mrs Cooper:)...who are dumb as soup.